export default [
    {
        question: "can",
        answer: "pouvoir, peux, peux, peut, pouvons, pouvez, peuvent"
    },
    {
        question: "can - Polite form",
        answer: "pouvoir, pourrais, pourrais, pourrait, pourrions, pourriez, pourraient"
    },
    {
        question: "must",
        answer: "devoir, dois, dois, doit, devons, devez, doivent"
    },
    {
        question: "Must  - polite form",
        answer: "devoir, devrais, devrais, devrait, devrions, devriez, devraient"
    },
    {
        question: "want",
        answer: "vouloir, veux, veux, veut, voulons, voulez, veulent"
    },
    {
        question: "Want - polite form",
        answer: "vouloir, voudrais, voudrais, voudrait, voudrions, voudriez, voudraient",
    },
    {
        question: "Leave",
        answer: "partir, pars, pars, part, parsons, parted, partner",
    },
    {
        question: "go out",
        answer: "sortir, sors, sors, sort, sortons, sortez, sortent",
    },
    {
        question: "sleep",
        answer: "dormir, dors, does, dort, dormons, dormez, dorment",
    },
    {
        question: "come",
        answer: "venir, viens, viens, vient, venons, venez, viennent",
    },
    {
        question: "hold",
        answer: "tenir, tiens, tiens, tient, tenons, tenez, tiennent",
    },
    {
        question: "become",
        answer: "devenir, deviens, deviens, devient, devenons, devenez, deviennent",
    },
    {
        question: "know in depth",
        answer: "Savoir, sais, sais, sait, savons, savez, savent",
    },
    {
        question: "finish",
        answer: "finir, finis, finis, finit, finissons, finissez, finissent",
    },
    {
        question: "choose",
        answer: "choisir, choisis, choisis, choisit, choisissons, choisissez, choisissent",
    },
    {
        question: "စာမေးပွဲဖြေနိုင် - succeed",
        answer: "réussir, réussis, réussis, réussit, réussissons, réussissez, réussissent",
    },
    {
        question: "open",
        answer: "ouvrir, ouvre, ouvres, ouvre, ouvrons, ouvrez, ouvrent",
    },
    {
        question: "see",
        answer: "voir, vois, vois, voit, voyons, voyez, voient",
    },
]